English 

* Deutsch
* English
* Français
* Polski
* Русский
* Español
* Türkçe

EUR - € 

* EUR - €
* USD - $
* PLN - zł
* GBP - £
* CHF - CHF
* RUB - ₽
* BRL - R$
* CAD - $
* AUD - $
* PHP - ₱
* MYR - MYR
* INR - ₹
* UAH - ₴

[](https://www.facebook.com/SkinBaronEN)[](https://twitter.com/skinbaronEN)[](https://www.instagram.com/skinbaronen/)[](https://steamcommunity.com/groups/SkinBaronDE)3D-Viewer[SmokeBaron](https://skinbaron.de/smokebaron)Screenshots

Light Dark

* Login

Privacy Statement
-----------------

We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our enterprise. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the SkinBaron GmbH. The use of the Internet pages of the SkinBaron GmbH is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is required, we refer to the legal basis of the General Data Protection Regulation, the Federal Data Protection Act and other laws relevant to data protection. If the law requires the consent of the data subject, we will of course obtain this before processing the data.

The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to the SkinBaron GmbH. By means of this data protection declaration, our enterprise would like to inform the general public of the nature, scope, and purpose of the personal data we collect, use and process. Furthermore, data subjects are informed, by means of this data protection declaration, of the rights to which they are entitled.

As the controller, the SkinBaron GmbH has implemented numerous technical and organizational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed through this website. However, Internet-based data transmissions may in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection may not be guaranteed.

### Contents

1. Definitions
2. Name and address of the controller
3. Purposes, legal bases and storage periods of personal data
    
    3.1 Art.6 I lit. b) GDPR: We process personal data because it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party or for the implementation of pre-contractual measures that are taken at the request of the data subject.
    
    3.2 Art.6 I lit. c) GDPR: We process personal data because the processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject.
    
    3.3 Art.6 lit. f) GDPR: We process personal data because the processing is necessary for the protection of a corrective interest of ours, unless the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject, which requires the protection of personal data, are overridden.
    
    3.4 Art.6 lit. a) DSG-VO: We process personal data if a corresponding consent of the purpose has been given.s
    
4. Privacy policy for the SmokeBaron App
5. Data protection provisions about the application and use of iDevAffiliate
6. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Facebook
7. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google Analytics (with anonymization function)
8. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google-AdWords
9. Data protection provisions about the application and use of X
10. Data protection provisions about the application and use of YouTube
11. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Cloudflare
12. Rights of the data subject
13. Routine erasure and blocking of personal data
14. Backup measures to protect against data loss & data theft

### 1\. Definitions

The data protection declaration of the SkinBaron GmbH is based on the terms used by the European legislator for the adoption of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Our data protection declaration should be legible and understandable for the general public, as well as our customers and business partners. To ensure this, we would like to first explain the terminology used.

In this data protection declaration, we use, inter alia, the following terms:

a)    Personal data

Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“data subject”). An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

b)    Data subject

Data subject is any identified or identifiable natural person, whose personal data is processed by the controller responsible for the processing.

c)    Processing

Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

d)    Restriction of processing

Restriction of processing is the marking of stored personal data with the aim of limiting their processing in the future.

e)    Profiling

Profiling means any form of automated processing of personal data consisting of the use of personal data to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person, in particular to analyse or predict aspects concerning that natural person's performance at work, economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behaviour, location or movements.

f)    Pseudonymisation

Pseudonymisation is the processing of personal data in such a manner that the personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the use of additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separately and is subject to technical and organisational measures to ensure that the personal data are not attributed to an identified or identifiable natural person.

g)    Controller or controller responsible for the processing

Controller or controller responsible for the processing is the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Union or Member State law, the controller or the specific criteria for its nomination may be provided for by Union or Member State law.

h)    Processor

Processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.

i)    Recipient

Recipient is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. However, public authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as recipients; the processing of those data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the processing.

j)    Third party

Third party is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.

k)    Consent

Consent of the data subject is any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the data subject's wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear affirmative action, signifies agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him or her.

### 2\. Name and address of the controller

Controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), other data protection laws applicable in Member states of the European Union and other provisions related to data protection is:

SkinBaron GmbH

Ossecker Straße 165

95030 Hof

Deutschland

E-Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://skinbaron.de/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Website: skinbaron.de

### 3\. Purposes, legal bases and storage periods of personal data

We process personal data for different purposes, based on different legal bases. Essentially, we process personal data to ensure the best possible user experience at SkinBaron, to enable individual suggestions for skins, to be able to get in touch with questions or suggestions, to detect fraudulent or illegal activities at an early stage, to thwart them and also to be able to prosecute them in cooperation with the authorities responsible for this.

In order to be able to explain to you in more detail for which purpose and on which legal basis personal data is processed by us, you will find a list below, sorted by the respective legal basis.

3.1 Art.6 I lit. b) GDPR: We process personal data because it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party or for the implementation of pre-contractual measures that are taken at the request of the data subject.

* At SkinBaron it is possible to purchase goods. For this purpose, it is necessary to collect personal data in the ordering process. The data entered in the order mask provided for this purpose will be transmitted to SkinBaron and stored. The data to be entered includes:
    * First and last name
    * residential address
    * date of birth
    * E-mail address
    * Bank accountA handling of the payment processes takes place through our partner, Adyen N.V. A transfer of this personal data thus takes place for the processing of a purchase contract. Adyen N.V. is a payment service provider that specializes in processing money transactions within the framework of legal requirements and guidelines. Adyen N.V. is thus independently responsible for the protection of this personal data within the meaning of the GDPR within the scope of this contract fulfilment.

3.2 Art.6 I lit. c) GDPR: We process personal data because the processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject.

* SkinBaron is subject to the Money Laundering Act, among other things, due to the form of business described. This requires that a contractual partner is to be identified before a business relationship is established. This is done at SkinBaron by entering the personal data in the respective input mask in the own profile. The following personal data has to be entered:
    * First and last name
    * residential address
    * date of birth
    * CitizenshipA transfer of this data to Adyen N.V. takes place within the framework of the legal regulations, in particular the customer care obligations of the Money Laundering Act.

3.3 Art.6 lit. f) GDPR: We process personal data because the processing is necessary for the protection of a corrective interest of ours, unless the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject, which requires the protection of personal data, are overridden.

* The website of the SkinBaron GmbH collects a series of general data and information with each call-up of the website by a data subject or automated system. This general data and information is stored in the log files of the server
* The browser types and versions used
* The operating system used by the accessing system
* The website from which an accessing system arrives at our website (so-called referrer).
* The sub-websites that are accessed via an accessing system on our website.
* The date and time of an access to the website
* An Internet Protocol (IP) address
* The Internet service provider of the accessing system
* Other similar data and information that serve to avert danger in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.

3.4 Art.6 lit. a) DSG-VO: We process personal data if a corresponding consent of the purpose has been given.

* In addition to the fulfilment of a purchase contract, SkinBaron has another purpose that requires the provision of the e-mail address. During registration it is necessary to provide an e-mail address. This is necessary so that there is a secured and confirmed contact between SkinBaron and user, in particular to inform about changes of the ToS & Privacy Policy in time and to re-establish the effectiveness therein by a consent to be obtained again. Furthermore, it is possible that a disclosure of the specified e-mail address is necessary for the prosecution of criminal offenses to authorities.
* The website of the SkinBaron GmbH contains legal requirements which enable a quick electronic contact to our enterprise, as well as direct communication with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or by using a contact form, the personal data transmitted by the data subject will be stored automatically. Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the controller will be stored for the purposes of processing or contacting the data subject. No disclosure of this personal data to third parties will take place.
* On the website of the SkinBaron GmbH, users are given the opportunity to subscribe to our enterprise's newsletter. The personal data transmitted to the controller when the newsletter is ordered is specified in the input mask used for this purpose. The SkinBaron GmbH informs its customers and business partners at regular intervals by means of a newsletter about enterprise offers. The newsletter of our enterprise can basically only be received by the data subject, if (1) the data subject has a valid e-mail address and (2) the data subject registers for the newsletter. For legal reasons, a confirmation e-mail is sent to the e-mail address registered by a data subject for the newsletter for the first time using the double opt-in procedure. This confirmation e-mail serves to verify whether the owner of the e-mail address as the data subject has authorized the receipt of the newsletter. When registering for the newsletter, we also store the IP address of the computer system used by the data subject at the time of registration, as assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP), as well as the date and time of registration. The collection of this data is necessary in order to be able to trace the (possible) misuse of the e-mail address of a data subject at a later point in time and therefore serves the legal safeguarding of the controller.
* The internet pages of SkinBaron GmbH use cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored on a computer system via an Internet browser. Numerous websites and servers use cookies. Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID. A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie. It consists of a string of characters by which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored. This enables the visited Internet pages and servers to distinguish the individual browser of the data subject from other Internet browsers that contain other cookies. A specific internet browser can be recognized and identified via the unique cookie ID. Through the use of cookies, the SkinBaron GmbH can provide the users of this website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without the cookie setting. By means of a cookie, the information and offers on our website can be optimized in the sense of the user. Cookies allow us, as already mentioned, to recognize the users of our website. The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users to use our website. For example, the user of a website that uses cookies does not have to re-enter his or her access data each time he or she visits the website, because this is handled by the website and the cookie stored on the user's computer system. Another example is the cookie of a shopping cart in an online store. The online store uses a cookie to remember the items that a customer has placed in the virtual shopping cart. The data subject can prevent the setting of cookies by our website at any time by means of an appropriate setting of the Internet browser used and thus permanently object to the setting of cookies. Furthermore, cookies that have already been set can be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all common Internet browsers. If the data subject deactivates the setting of cookies in the Internet browser used, not all functions of our website may be fully usable.
* To enable SkinBaron to provide individualized and user-tailored suggestions for goods and items, the user's behaviour, especially with regard to
    * the IP address
    * of the country indicated by the user during the registration process
    * of purchasing behaviour
    * the selected payment method
    * of the usage behaviour on the websiteanalysed. This analysis can also ensure future marketing campaigns, general and specific improvements to the website and the connection of new products. At no time does this involve automated decision-making that would significantly affect the data subject.

### 4\. Privacy policy for the SmokeBaron App

SmokeBaron is an app that shows video instructions on how to throw objects, especially hand grenades, smoke grenades, stun grenades and Molotov cocktails, in the computer game: CounterStrike. This app can be found for free in all popular app purchasing programs. The App is owned by the above-mentioned SkinBaron GmbH, which also makes it the data controller.

We do not collect any personal data. You can use the "Sign in through Steam"-Service provided by Valve Corporation in our app to save certain information for example your favourite smoke grenades. This sign in is optional, it is not necessary to use the app. By using this option, you give us the consent due to Article 6 I lit. a) GDPR to do so. When "Sign in through Steam" is used the following information is saved to our database:

* your steam id
* the hardware id of your mobile device
* the time of the login
* your steam profile picture url
* your steam nickname

This information will be stored if you have given consent for it. If you revoke your consent, this information will be deleted right away.

Our App is hosted within the European Economic Area ("EEA") and your personal data will be stored by ALL-INKL.COM, Hauptstraße 68, D-02742 Friedersdorf.

For the purpose of a shorter loading time, we use a so-called Content Delivery Network ("CDN") for some offers. With this service, content, e.g., large media files, are delivered via regionally distributed servers of external CDN service providers. Therefore, access data is processed on the servers of the service providers. Our service providers work for us within the framework of order processing. If you have any questions about our service providers and the basis of our cooperation with them, please use the contact option described in this privacy policy.

Meier Tobias, Rosenthal Jürgen GbR ("Stadtrausch") have access to the information mentioned in chapter 2, but they will only use this information for app optimization purposes.

### 5\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of iDevAffiliate

On this website, the controller has integrated components of the enterprise iDevAffiliate Inc. iDevAffiliate is an affiliate network based in the USA, which offers affiliate marketing.

Affiliate marketing is a web-based form of distribution, which allows commercial operators of Internet sites, the so-called merchants or advertisers, to show advertising, which will be paid mostly through click or sale commissions, on third-party Internet sites that are also called affiliates or publishers. The Merchant provides through the affiliate network an advertising medium, such as an advertising banner or other suitable means of Internet advertising, which is subsequently integrated by an affiliate on its own Internet pages or via other channels such as keyword advertising or e-mail marketing.

The operating company of Affilinet is the iDevAffiliate Inc., 23816 Woodpark Ct., Valencia, 91354, California, USA

iDevAffiliate sets a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. The definition of cookies is explained above. The tracking cookie by iDevAffiliate stores no personal data. Only the identification number of the affiliate, that is, the partner mediating the potential customer, as well as the ordinal number of the visitor of a website and the clicked advertising medium are stored. The purpose of this data storage is the processing of commission payments between a merchant and affiliate, which are processed through the affiliate network, that is iDevAffiliate.

The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the Internet browser used and, thus, permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent iDevAffiliate from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. In addition, cookies already in use by iDevAffiliate may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.

The applicable data protection provisions of iDevAffiliate may be accessed under https://www.idevdirect.com/policies.php

### 6\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Facebook

On this website, the controller has integrated components of the enterprise Facebook. Facebook is a social network.

A social network is a place for social meetings on the Internet, an online community, which usually allows users to communicate with each other and interact in a virtual space. A social network may serve as a platform for the exchange of opinions and experiences, or enable the Internet community to provide personal or business-related information. Facebook allows social network users to include the creation of private profiles, upload photos, and network through friend requests.

The operating company of Facebook is Facebook, Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA 94025, United States. If a person lives outside of the United States or Canada, the controller is the Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Ireland.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet website, which is operated by the controller and into which a Facebook component (Facebook plug-ins) was integrated, the web browser on the information technology system of the data subject is automatically prompted to download display of the corresponding Facebook component from Facebook through the Facebook component. An overview of all the Facebook Plug-ins may be accessed under https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/. During the course of this technical procedure, Facebook is made aware of what specific sub-site of our website was visited by the data subject.

If the data subject is logged in at the same time on Facebook, Facebook detects with every call-up to our website by the data subject—and for the entire duration of their stay on our Internet site—which specific sub-site of our Internet page was visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the Facebook component and associated with the respective Facebook account of the data subject. If the data subject clicks on one of the Facebook buttons integrated into our website, e.g. the "Like" button, or if the data subject submits a comment, then Facebook matches this information with the personal Facebook user account of the data subject and stores the personal data.

Facebook always receives, through the Facebook component, information about a visit to our website by the data subject, whenever the data subject is logged in at the same time on Facebook during the time of the call-up to our website. This occurs regardless of whether the data subject clicks on the Facebook component or not. If such a transmission of information to Facebook is not desirable for the data subject, then he or she may prevent this by logging off from their Facebook account before a call-up to our website is made.

The data protection guideline published by Facebook, which is available at https://facebook.com/about/privacy/, provides information about the collection, processing and use of personal data by Facebook. In addition, it is explained there what setting options Facebook offers to protect the privacy of the data subject. In addition, different configuration options are made available to allow the elimination of data transmission to Facebook. These applications may be used by the data subject to eliminate a data transmission to Facebook.

### 7\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google Analytics (with anonymization function)

On this website, the controller has integrated the component of Google Analytics (with the anonymizer function). Google Analytics is a web analytics service. Web analytics is the collection, gathering, and analysis of data about the behavior of visitors to websites. A web analysis service collects, inter alia, data about the website from which a person has come (the so-called referrer), which sub-pages were visited, or how often and for what duration a sub-page was viewed. Web analytics are mainly used for the optimization of a website and in order to carry out a cost-benefit analysis of Internet advertising.

The operator of the Google Analytics component is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States./p>

For the web analytics through Google Analytics the controller uses the application "\_gat. \_anonymizeIp". By means of this application the IP address of the Internet connection of the data subject is abridged by Google and anonymised when accessing our websites from a Member State of the European Union or another Contracting State to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.

The purpose of the Google Analytics component is to analyze the traffic on our website. Google uses the collected data and information, inter alia, to evaluate the use of our website and to provide online reports, which show the activities on our websites, and to provide other services concerning the use of our Internet site for us.

Google Analytics places a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. The definition of cookies is explained above. With the setting of the cookie, Google is enabled to analyze the use of our website. With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and into which a Google Analytics component was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject will automatically submit data through the Google Analytics component for the purpose of online advertising and the settlement of commissions to Google. During the course of this technical procedure, the enterprise Google gains knowledge of personal information, such as the IP address of the data subject, which serves Google, inter alia, to understand the origin of visitors and clicks, and subsequently create commission settlements.

The cookie is used to store personal information, such as the access time, the location from which the access was made, and the frequency of visits of our website by the data subject. With each visit to our Internet site, such personal data, including the IP address of the Internet access used by the data subject, will be transmitted to Google in the United States of America. These personal data are stored by Google in the United States of America. Google may pass these personal data collected through the technical procedure to third parties.

The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent Google Analytics from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. In addition, cookies already in use by Google Analytics may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.

In addition, the data subject has the possibility of objecting to a collection of data that are generated by Google Analytics, which is related to the use of this website, as well as the processing of this data by Google and the chance to preclude any such. For this purpose, the data subject must download a browser add-on under the link https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and install it. This browser add-on tells Google Analytics through a JavaScript, that any data and information about the visits of Internet pages may not be transmitted to Google Analytics. The installation of the browser add-ons is considered an objection by Google. If the information technology system of the data subject is later deleted, formatted, or newly installed, then the data subject must reinstall the browser add-ons to disable Google Analytics. If the browser add-on was uninstalled by the data subject or any other person who is attributable to their sphere of competence, or is disabled, it is possible to execute the reinstallation or reactivation of the browser add-ons.

Further information and the applicable data protection provisions of Google may be retrieved under https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ and under http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html. Google Analytics is further explained under the following Link https://www.google.com/analytics/.

### 8\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google-AdWords

On this website, the controller has integrated Google AdWords. Google AdWords is a service for Internet advertising that allows the advertiser to place ads in Google search engine results and the Google advertising network. Google AdWords allows an advertiser to pre-define specific keywords with the help of which an ad on Google's search results only then displayed, when the user utilizes the search engine to retrieve a keyword-relevant search result. In the Google Advertising Network, the ads are distributed on relevant web pages using an automatic algorithm, taking into account the previously defined keywords.

The operating company of Google AdWords is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, UNITED STATES.

The purpose of Google AdWords is the promotion of our website by the inclusion of relevant advertising on the websites of third parties and in the search engine results of the search engine Google and an insertion of third-party advertising on our website.

If a data subject reaches our website via a Google ad, a conversion cookie is filed on the information technology system of the data subject through Google. The definition of cookies is explained above. A conversion cookie loses its validity after 30 days and is not used to identify the data subject. If the cookie has not expired, the conversion cookie is used to check whether certain sub-pages, e.g, the shopping cart from an online shop system, were called up on our website. Through the conversion cookie, both Google and the controller can understand whether a person who reached an AdWords ad on our website generated sales, that is, executed or canceled a sale of goods.

The data and information collected through the use of the conversion cookie is used by Google to create visit statistics for our website. These visit statistics are used in order to determine the total number of users who have been served through AdWords ads to ascertain the success or failure of each AdWords ad and to optimize our AdWords ads in the future. Neither our company nor other Google AdWords advertisers receive information from Google that could identify the data subject.

The conversion cookie stores personal information, e.g. the Internet pages visited by the data subject. Each time we visit our Internet pages, personal data, including the IP address of the Internet access used by the data subject, is transmitted to Google in the United States of America. These personal data are stored by Google in the United States of America. Google may pass these personal data collected through the technical procedure to third parties.

The data subject may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies by our website, as stated above, by means of a corresponding setting of the Internet browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such a setting of the Internet browser used would also prevent Google from placing a conversion cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. In addition, a cookie set by Google AdWords may be deleted at any time via the Internet browser or other software programs.

The data subject has a possibility of objecting to the interest based advertisement of Google. Therefore, the data subject must access from each of the browsers in use the link www.google.de/settings/ads and set the desired settings.

Further information and the applicable data protection provisions of Google may be retrieved under https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.

### 9\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of X

On this website, the controller has integrated components of X. X is a multilingual, publicly-accessible microblogging service on which users may publish and spread so-called ‘posts,’ e.g. short messages, which are limited to 280 characters. These short messages are available for everyone, including those who are not logged on to X. The posts are also displayed to so-called followers of the respective user. Followers are other X users who follow a user's posts. Furthermore, X allows you to address a wide audience via hashtags, links or reposts.

The operating company of X is X, Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a X component (X button) was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject is automatically prompted to download a display of the corresponding X component of X. Further information about the X buttons is available under https://about.X.com/de/resources/buttons. During the course of this technical procedure, X gains knowledge of what specific sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject. The purpose of the integration of the X component is a retransmission of the contents of this website to allow our users to introduce this web page to the digital world and increase our visitor numbers.

If the data subject is logged in at the same time on X, X detects with every call-up to our website by the data subject and for the entire duration of their stay on our Internet site which specific sub-page of our Internet page was visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the X component and associated with the respective X account of the data subject. If the data subject clicks on one of the X buttons integrated on our website, then X assigns this information to the personal X user account of the data subject and stores the personal data.

X receives information via the X component that the data subject has visited our website, provided that the data subject is logged in on X at the time of the call-up to our website. This occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on the X component or not. If such a transmission of information to X is not desirable for the data subject, then he or she may prevent this by logging off from their X account before a call-up to our website is made.

The applicable data protection provisions of X may be accessed under https://X.com/privacy?lang=en.

### 10\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of YouTube

On this website, the controller has integrated components of YouTube. YouTube is an Internet video portal that enables video publishers to set video clips and other users free of charge, which also provides free viewing, review and commenting on them. YouTube allows you to publish all kinds of videos, so you can access both full movies and TV broadcasts, as well as music videos, trailers, and videos made by users via the Internet portal.

The operating company of YouTube is YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, UNITED STATES. The YouTube, LLC is a subsidiary of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a YouTube component (YouTube video) was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject is automatically prompted to download a display of the corresponding YouTube component. Further information about YouTube may be obtained under https://www.youtube.com/yt/about/en/. During the course of this technical procedure, YouTube and Google gain knowledge of what specific sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject.

If the data subject is logged in on YouTube, YouTube recognizes with each call-up to a sub-page that contains a YouTube video, which specific sub-page of our Internet site was visited by the data subject. This information is collected by YouTube and Google and assigned to the respective YouTube account of the data subject.

YouTube and Google will receive information through the YouTube component that the data subject has visited our website, if the data subject at the time of the call to our website is logged in on YouTube; this occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on a YouTube video or not. If such a transmission of this information to YouTube and Google is not desirable for the data subject, the delivery may be prevented if the data subject logs off from their own YouTube account before a call-up to our website is made.

YouTube's data protection provisions, available at https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/, provide information about the collection, processing and use of personal data by YouTube and Google.

### 11\. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Cloudflare

On this website, the controller has integrated Cloudflare. Cloudflare is a US company headquartered in California, which is intended to protect our website esp. from so-called DDoS attacks.

A DDoS attack is a special type of cyber crime. The distributed denial of service (DDoS) attack is a "distributed" denial of service (DoS) attack, which in turn is a service blockade. This occurs when a requested service is no longer available or only available to a very limited extent. In most cases, this is triggered by a deliberate overload of the IT infrastructure. Attackers use this type of cybercrime to extort ransoms from unprotected organizations or to carry out, cover up or prepare other criminal acts.

The operating company is Cloudflare, Inc, 101 Townsend St, San Francisco, CA 94107.

The contact person regarding data protection-related matters in Germany is Cloudflare Germany GmbH, Rosental 7, 80331 Munich, Germany.

The central contact regarding data protection-related matters is [\[email protected\]](https://skinbaron.de/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) (subject: Data Protection Officer).

Cloudflare processes users' interactions with our website ("Cloudflare processes End Users' interactions with Customer's Internet Properties and the Services.") to identify attackers and prevent site overload ("Cloudflare only processes personal information in a way that is compatible with and relevant to the purpose for which it was collected or authorized.").

The data is processed only for business purposes.

Cloudflare sets a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. What cookies are has already been explained above. By setting the cookie, Cloudflare is enabled to analyze the user of our website. The cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information. However, it enables Cloudflare to detect malicious behavior and improve the protection of the website.

Cloudflare's applicable privacy policy can be found at https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/.

### 12\. Rights of the data subject

a) Right of confirmation

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her are being processed. If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of confirmation, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

b) Right of access

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller free information about his or her personal data stored at any time and a copy of this information. Furthermore, the European directives and regulations grant the data subject access to the following information:

* the purposes of the processing;
* the categories of personal data concerned;
* the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations;
* where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;
* the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of personal data, or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data subject, or to object to such processing;
* the existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;
* where the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available information as to their source;
* the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in Article 22(1) and (4) of the GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subject.
* Furthermore, the data subject shall have a right to obtain information as to whether personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation. Where this is the case, the data subject shall have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards relating to the transfer.

If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of access, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

c) Right to rectification

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning him or her. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject shall have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.

If a data subject wishes to exercise this right to rectification, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.

d) Right to erasure (Right to be forgotten)

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning him or her without undue delay, and the controller shall have the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where one of the following grounds applies, as long as the processing is not necessary:

The personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed.

The data subject withdraws consent to which the processing is based according to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, and where there is no other legal ground for the processing.

The data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(2) of the GDPR.

The personal data have been unlawfully processed.

The personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject.

The personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Article 8(1) of the GDPR.

If one of the aforementioned reasons applies, and a data subject wishes to request the erasure of personal data stored by the SkinBaron GmbH, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller. An employee of SkinBaron GmbH shall promptly ensure that the erasure request is complied with immediately.

Where the controller has made personal data public and is obliged pursuant to Article 17(1) to erase the personal data, the controller, taking account of available technology and the cost of implementation, shall take reasonable steps, including technical measures, to inform other controllers processing the personal data that the data subject has requested erasure by such controllers of any links to, or copy or replication of, those personal data, as far as processing is not required. An employees of the SkinBaron GmbH will arrange the necessary measures in individual cases.

e) Right of restriction of processing

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller restriction of processing where one of the following applies:

The accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject, for a period enabling the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data.

The processing is unlawful and the data subject opposes the erasure of the personal data and requests instead the restriction of their use instead.

The controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

The data subject has objected to processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of the controller override those of the data subject.

If one of the aforementioned conditions is met, and a data subject wishes to request the restriction of the processing of personal data stored by the SkinBaron GmbH, he or she may at any time contact any employee of the controller. The employee of the SkinBaron GmbH will arrange the restriction of the processing.

f) Right to data portability

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator, to receive the personal data concerning him or her, which was provided to a controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. He or she shall have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the controller to which the personal data have been provided, as long as the processing is based on consent pursuant to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, or on a contract pursuant to point (b) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, and the processing is carried out by automated means, as long as the processing is not necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.

Furthermore, in exercising his or her right to data portability pursuant to Article 20(1) of the GDPR, the data subject shall have the right to have personal data transmitted directly from one controller to another, where technically feasible and when doing so does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

In order to assert the right to data portability, the data subject may at any time contact any employee of the SkinBaron GmbH.

g) Right to object

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to object, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, at any time, to processing of personal data concerning him or her, which is based on point (e) or (f) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR. This also applies to profiling based on these provisions.

The SkinBaron GmbH shall no longer process the personal data in the event of the objection, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

If the SkinBaron GmbH processes personal data for direct marketing purposes, the data subject shall have the right to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning him or her for such marketing. This applies to profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing. If the data subject objects to the SkinBaron GmbH to the processing for direct marketing purposes, the SkinBaron GmbH will no longer process the personal data for these purposes.

In addition, the data subject has the right, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, to object to processing of personal data concerning him or her by the SkinBaron GmbH for scientific or historical research purposes, or for statistical purposes pursuant to Article 89(1) of the GDPR, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.

In order to exercise the right to object, the data subject may contact any employee of the SkinBaron GmbH. In addition, the data subject is free in the context of the use of information society services, and notwithstanding Directive 2002/58/EC, to use his or her right to object by automated means using technical specifications.

h) Automated individual decision-making, including profiling

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning him or her, or similarly significantly affects him or her, as long as the decision (1) is not is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) is not authorised by Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject and which also lays down suitable measures to safeguard the data subject's rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, or (3) is not based on the data subject's explicit consent.

If the decision (1) is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) it is based on the data subject's explicit consent, the SkinBaron GmbH shall implement suitable measures to safeguard the data subject's rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, at least the right to obtain human intervention on the part of the controller, to express his or her point of view and contest the decision.

If the data subject wishes to exercise the rights concerning automated individual decision-making, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the SkinBaron GmbH.

i) Right to withdraw data protection consent

Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to withdraw his or her consent to processing of his or her personal data at any time.

If the data subject wishes to exercise the right to withdraw the consent, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the SkinBaron GmbH.

### 13\. Routine erasure and blocking of personal data

The data controller shall process and store the personal data of the data subject only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of storage, or as far as this is granted by the European legislator or other legislators in laws or regulations to which the controller is subject to.

If the storage purpose is not applicable, or if a storage period prescribed by the European legislator or another competent legislator expires, the personal data are routinely blocked or erased in accordance with legal requirements.

The retention periods for contracts and the personal data collected for them generally last between six and ten years. Insofar as there are legal regulations, the data is then blocked or anonymized instead of being deleted. This is particularly necessary if it is required for legal prosecution or legal defence.

Other statutory provisions on the retention of data result, among other things, from the Money Laundering Act. This stipulates that the data collected to establish a business relationship must be stored for five years, starting at the end of the year in which the business relationship ends.

For other purposes, in particular when processing data on the basis of a given consent, the processing ends when the consent is revoked. Storage of this previously processed personal data does not take place. To the extent permitted by law, blocking or anonymization instead of deletion also takes place here in order to be able to

### 14\. Backup measures to protect against data loss & data theft

The security of data in relation to the use and user experience at SkinBaron is a great responsibility and is accordingly measured with a high value. In order to not only simply comply with legal regulations, SkinBaron GmbH is committed to consistently guarantee optimal protection of personal data against loss, misuse or theft within the framework of technological progress. Extensive technical and organizational measures, specially trained and educated employees, a team of experts in their field and the claim to guarantee the highest level of security within the user experience at SkinBaron is the basic attitude with which we process personal data. Since personal data processing always requires two parties (controller and data subject), events may still occur where data cannot be processed properly. This is in the nature of things when data is transmitted via public networks. SkinBaron has no influence on this, as it is also the responsibility of the data subject to ensure in particular the correct transmission and use of their own data.

Print

Your benefits with us
---------------------

### Save

On SkinBaron.de, you pay on average 30% less for CS2 skins than on the community marketplace

### 1 million CS2 skins

Discover a variety of CS2 skins and save real money with our marketplace filters

### Real money

Or simply sell your CS2 skins for real money and then have the funds transferred to you via bank transfer.

### Skin trades

Manage your CS2 skins, payouts, and sales quickly and easily in your SkinBaron profile - your hub for CS2 skin trades.

### 3D viewer

With our 3D viewer, you can take a detailed look at the CS2 skins that interest you before making a purchase.

Support +

* Contact

Services +

* 3D-Viewer
* Screenshots

Get to know us +

Pay securely with +

* footer.payment\_options.sofort
* footer.payment\_options.paysafecard
* footer.payment\_options.cartesbancaires
* footer.payment\_options.mastercard
* footer.payment\_options.visa
* footer.payment\_options.ideal
* footer.payment\_options.mobilepay
* footer.payment\_options.googlepay
* footer.payment\_options.sepa

Follow us +

EN | EUR (€)

© 2024 SkinBaron GmbH

Currently unavailable
